newretrowave.com 2016-04-11

# Privacy Policy — NewRetroWave | Stay Retro! | Live The 80's Dream! |

### Effective as of Sept 26, 2014

Your privacy is important to us. None of us at NRW would want our own personal information used in ways we do not agree to or know about.

Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy below to make sure you understand and agree with it.

### Why does NRW collect personal information?

We need your personal information (i.e., information by which you are individually identifiable) in order to provide you our services, pay you (music submissions only), get your music to our partners, answer questions you may have, provide customer support, provide new opportunities, and deliver new products, updates and a high quality customer experience.

### What exact information does NRW collect?

To offer you our services and products, NRW will need basic personal information from you that might consist of all or part of the following: your physical address; email address; phone numbers; credit/charge card information to collect from you various fees and charges for purchased products; bank account and/or PayPal account information for deposits of money owed to you from the sale of your music. 

NRW may also collect non-personal information from you, including the names of your songs and albums and the associated artists; the year that your recordings were made/released; and the name(s) of the person or entity that owns and controls the rights to the songs, albums and/or artwork that you deliver to NRW (music submissions only). Such information may, without limitation, be used to keep track of how certain albums and/or songs are selling for ranking charts. From time to time NRW might also present you with a voluntary survey or questionnaire about our current or possible future services or products that solicits non-personal information from you.

### Does NRW disclose your personal information to anyone?

We take your privacy very seriously. In order to serve you it is possible that people working for NRW might view your personal information to make sure we are providing you with the best service possible, but such access will be on a need-to-know basis only and they will be required to keep your personal information confidential and use it only as provided by the NRW privacy policy. 

It is also possible that with improvements to existing services or with the addition of new services it may be to your advantage for NRW to make specific personal information about you available to companies that NRW has a strategic relationship with or that perform work for NRW so that they can provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. We will provide these companies with only the personal information that they require to perform the task for which they have been hired to do.  **These companies must also protect your personal information in accordance with NRW's privacy policy.**  Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to sell your music, upload your songs, upload your album artwork, purchase products and services, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers and content on the NRW website.

Your personal information may also be disclosed to law enforcement officials or third parties if NRW is required to do so by law. Furthermore, in the event that TuneCore receives notification that any content you have posted online using the NRW service infringes on the rights of a third party, NRW may, in its good faith discretion, disclose your contact information to such third party.

### How does NRW protect your personal information?

NRW will take appropriate administrative, technical, physical measures and more to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft or misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

Although there will always be people attempting to steal information, we follow the industry accepted security standards designed to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access to, disclosure of and use of your personal information. We use Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) encryption for credit card and other bank transactions. Due to this level of security, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Netscape Navigator 3.0 (or a later version), or Internet Explorer. Doing so protects the confidentiality of your personal information while in transit over the Internet. NRW has used and will continue to use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your personal information.

In addition, NRW will restrict employee access to databases containing personal information and impose confidentiality requirements upon employees who need to know such information. Furthermore, any NRW employee with partial or total access to personal information must abide by the terms of this privacy policy.

### Accuracy of your personal information:

NRW works hard to keep your personal information safe, accurate, complete and as current as possible. 

### Internet Protocol (“IP”) Addresses, cookies and other variables:

As is the case with many websites, the NRW website logs your IP address and uses standard technology called cookies, which are small data files that are downloaded onto your computer when you visit the NRW website. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the NRW website server whenever you interact with the NRW website. We use cookies and the information they provide to improve our services and the quality of your experience while visiting the NRW website.

You can set your browser to notify you when a cookie is enabled, allowing you the opportunity to reject or disable the cookie; however, it is possible that some portion or functions of the NRW website or its participating partners' websites may not work as well or at all if you disable your cookies.

We may use third party service providers for the limited purpose to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online campaigns or analyze visitor activity on the NRW website. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for NRW.

Many websites gather certain non-personal information automatically and store it in log files, including things like your IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. None of this information identifies you directly. NRW may also enable this technology for use in ways that are commonly accepted by industry practice.

### Message boards, chat rooms and instant messaging:

In the event that NRW launches community-based services such as message boards, blogs, instant messaging and other similar services, you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users.  **Please note that information that you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. NRW is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums – you are solely responsible for any content that you post there, including, but not limited to, any personal information that you choose to reveal in these public forums.**  In using any of these services, you agree that you will not use them for any purpose that is unlawful or in violation of NRW’s Terms and Conditions. Please note that NRW may, in its sole discretion, monitor postings in these forums to assure that users are complying with the NRW Terms and Conditions.

### Links to other websites:

 **It is possible that at some time NRW might link to other websites. If we do, and you choose to go to these other websites, please be aware that such websites may not be affiliated with NRW and are not subject to NRW’s Privacy Policy. We encourage you to carefully review such other websites’ respective privacy policies and ask questions directly of them in this regard.**

### Changes to NRW’s Privacy Policy:

As NRW grows, changes, and expands to suit your needs, we may need to modify, alter or otherwise update this privacy policy.  **When we make changes to this Privacy Policy we will notify you here, so we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time.**  We may also attempt to notify you of any such changes to our Privacy Policy via email or by placing a notice on our home page, but are not required to do so.

### Acceptance of NRW’s Privacy Policy:

 **By using the NRW website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by NRW in accordance with this Privacy Policy.**

### Questions about NRW’s Privacy Policy:

If you have any questions, concerns or thoughts about the privacy of your personal information while using the NRW website or this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at our Contact Page.
